(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Nakiri Ayame 6th BirthDay ~Shoot the heart~
NAKIRI AYAME BIRTHDAY LIVE
Thank you for coming
LIVE GUEST
Say ho!
Say yo, yo!
よっしゃ、みんなで掛け声いくぞ！
Alright, let's do the chant together!
ワン、ツー、ワンツーーせーの！
One, two, one-two-go!
あ、掛け声決めてなかったな！
Ah, I hadn't decided on a chant!
ええええ！？
Whaaaat!?
そんなところもかわ世！！
Even that part is adorable!!
みんな寄こして恋恋
Everyone, come on over
たまにボーッとしておいおい
Sometimes spacing out, hey hey
次は歌えばよいよい
Next, it's good to sing
この道を進むのだ
Let's move forward on this path
あ、でもね疲れたらゆっくりと歩みましょう
Ah, but if you're tired, let's walk slowly
人生なんて気楽に構えましょう
Let's take life easy
なんて言ってたら「ちゃんとしろ」って
When I say that, they say "get it together"
どっち どっち どっち？
Which one, which one, which one?
どっちの君も大正解
Either version of you is the right answer
だってこの世はめちゃかわ世！
Because this world is super adorable!
ダメなところもなおかわ世
Even the bad parts are still adorable
生まれてきてくれてありがtoね
Thank you for being born
みんな大体大大大好き
I love everyone pretty much, very very much
ねぇねぇ そんなこんな世はかわ世？
Hey hey, isn't this and that kind of world adorable?
愛をくれる君かわ世！！
You, who gives me love, are adorable!!
ラブこそまさにラブだから
Because love is exactly what love is
余りあるかわまま世 創りましょ！！
Let's create an overflowing world of charm!!
あんまり振り回しすぎたら
If I toss and turn too much
もしかして呆れられちゃうかな？
Maybe you'll get fed up with me?
懲りずにね 愛してほしいな
I want you to love me without giving up
そんなところもかわ世
Even that part is adorable
あら？これ二番始まってる？
Huh? Is the second verse starting?
心配は気にしてらんない！
I can't be bothered with worries!
ちょっと心配になってきた...
I'm starting to get a little worried...
日々は夢駆ける勝ち抜きなれ
Days are a tournament to run for dreams
本日もお仕事がんばりましょう
Let's do our best at work today too
でもなー
But...
自分のペースでまったりもしたいしなー
I also want to relax at my own pace
どっち どっち どっち？
Which one, which one, which one?
んー、どっちの君も大優等
Mmm, either version of you is an honor student
だってこの世はめちゃかわ世！
Because this world is super adorable!
ダメなときもいいときも
In bad times and good times
どっちもあるから愛に気づく
I realize love because both exist
大体が大大大好きな結果
The result of loving almost everything very very much
ちょっとグダグダな足取りも
Even slightly clumsy steps
うまくいかない一日も
And days that don't go well
生きてるだけでかわなのだ
Just being alive is adorable
手前かわな上にかわを綴らず
Adding more cuteness on top of it
だってこの世は鬼かわ世！
Because this world is devilishly adorable!
不完全なところこそかわ世
Incomplete parts are exactly what's adorable
出会ってくれてありがtoね
Thank you for meeting me
みんな大体大大大好きで
I love everyone pretty much, very very much
百点！！
One hundred points!!
余はかわよ
I am kawayo
出会いも別れも君とかわよ
Both meeting and parting are kawayo with you
ラブって実はラバーなので
Love is actually about being lovers, so
甘々にかわの世を創りましょ！
Let's create a sweet, kawayo world!
あまり振り回しすぎたら
If I swing it around too much
もししかして呆れられちゃうかな
Maybe you'll get fed up with me?
懲りずにね 愛してほしいな
Don't give up, I want you to love me
そんな言葉も言えないし
I can't even say words like that
いつも器用にできないけど
I can't always do things skillfully, but
いつだって君が笑えるように
So that you can always smile
頑張るので 愛してほしいな
I'll do my best, so I want you to love me
そんなところもかわよ！
Even those parts are kawayo!
なんて世界がかわよ！
What a kawayo world!
今ここすべてがかわよ！
Right here, right now, everything is kawayo!
ワン、ツー、さん、しー
One, two, three, four
ディスコミュ星人 作詞：ナユタン星人 / ナナヲアカリ 作曲：ナユタン星人
Discommu Seijin Lyrics: Nayutalien / Nanawa Akari Composition: Nayutalien
まず朝起きたらチェック・ザ・通知
First, when I wake up, check the notifications
軽々未来コミュニケーション
Lighthearted future communication
小粋なジョークでダンス・ザ・通信
Witty jokes and dance-the-communication
フロアを沸かせ おやゆびで
Rock the floor with your thumb
そろそろ時間だ 外に出なきゃ
It's about time, I have to go out
通るはもちろん裏通り
I take the backstreets, of course
誰にも会わずにゴールインのはずが
I was supposed to reach the goal without meeting anyone,
まさかの気になるあの人が
But unexpectedly, that person I'm interested in...
おはよう！
Good morning!
「エッ！？エトアノ･･･ナンデココニイルノ･･･デスカ･･･！？アノ今日ソノ･･･」
“Eh!? Um... uh... why are you here...!? Um, today, that is...”
「どうしたの？」
“What's wrong?”
「イヤ･･･イェア、ソ、チョット･･･ド、ドウカシワ イヤ！アノ、エ、エ、イ･･･？」
“No... yeah, s- just... wh- what should I say? No! Um, e- e- i...?”
「うわあああ！」
“Waaaaah!”
デ、デ、ディスコミュニケーション
Di-di-discommunication
あなたと電波交信
Radio communication with you
まるでできない言葉がでない
I can't do it at all, the words won't come out
ちゅ、ちゅ、宙に舞っちゃうくらい
Like I'm dancing in the air
フィーリングで通じあいたい
I want to communicate through feelings
マジでできない 伝わりゃしない あー
I really can't do it, I can't get through, ah
星の数の言葉の中から
From among words as many as the stars
ひとつ何かを探してる
I'm searching for one something
伝えたいのに しかし、あたしは
I want to tell you, but I am...
ディスコミュ星人だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ
A discommu alien, da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
マイワールドならマイペースで思い通り
In my world, everything goes my way at my pace
イェイ！先制必勝 イン・ザ・グッド・ショーみたいな
Yay! Preemptive victory, like being in a good show
絶対負けない メゲない ショゲない 弱音は吐かない
Never losing, not getting discouraged, not getting depressed, not complaining
スポットライトでキラキラ輝く キラッとライクなあたし
Shining bright in the spotlight, the sparkling like-able me
あー 1.2.3.4 5.6.7.8
Ah, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
アドレナリン空回りだったり それでも笑顔でキュルキュルリン
Adrenaline running in neutral, but still smiling and kyun-kyun-ring
プリンセスでいいでしょ？ それしか似合わないんです
It's okay to be a princess, right? That's the only thing that suits me
目をみてしまえばみんなイチコロ そういうあたしが大好き！
Once I look into their eyes, everyone's a goner, I love that side of me!
「え！急にみんなとうしたの！？アリガト！」
“Eh! What happened to everyone all of a sudden!? Thanks!”
「いやあ、そんなこと言われても照れるというかナンというか(笑)」
“Well, even if you say that, I'm embarrassed, or something like that (lol)”
「エ！うわ～困ったな(笑)」
“Eh! Wow, I'm in trouble (lol)”
「ありがとう嬉しいな、アタシも･･････」
“Thank you, I'm happy, me too...”
あ、夢か。
Ah, it was a dream.
デ、デ、ディスコミュニケーション
Di-di-discommunication
あなたの感情予想
Predicting your emotions
まるでできない 答えがでない
I can't do it at all, no answer comes out
チュ、チュ、チューじゃ足りないくらい
Chu, chu, even a kiss isn't enough
フィーリングで感じあって
Feeling each other through feelings
そのまま溶けて･･･とか、そんな妄想中
Just melting away like that... or something, I'm in the middle of a delusion
デ、デ、ディスコミュニケーション
Di-di-discommunication
解答例的なナレーション
Narration like a sample answer
ガチでできない 伝わりゃしない あー
I really can't do it, I can't get through, ah
夢の中なら上手くできるの
In my dreams, I can do it well
だけどリアルじゃできやしない
But I can't do it in reality
伝えたいほど挙動る心は 同じ言語じゃないみたいなら
The more I want to tell you, the more my heart flutters, if it's like we're not speaking the same language...
星の数の言葉は捨てるよ！ 気持ちはほら、ここにあるよ！
I'll throw away words as many as the stars! Look, my feelings are right here!
伝えてみるさ だってあたしは
I'll try to tell you, because I am...
ディスコミュ星人だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ・だ
A discommu alien, da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
なんでもないです
It's nothing
はーい！ということで！
Haaai! And with that!
皆さん、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you for coming today!
1曲目は、余の1番最新のオリジナル曲、
The first song was my latest original song,
「かわよ」でしたー！
“Kawayo”!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
「かわよ」はね、フォースかな？
“Kawayo” was, at Fourth, I think?
フォースでお披露目した曲なんですけど
It's a song I premiered at Fourth,
今回が2回目になります！
And this is the second time [performing it]!
どうだったかな？「かわよ」でした！
How was it? That was “Kawayo”!
ということで皆さん合いの手してくれましたかー？
So, everyone, did you do the calls and chants?
そして続いて2曲目はディスコミュ星人！
And next, for the second song, it was 'Disco-mu Seijin'!
余もともともディスコミュ星人めっちゃ好きだったんですけど、
I've always really liked 'Disco-mu Seijin', but...
この曲ちょっと難しかったですね。
...this song was a bit difficult, wasn't it?
ちょっとあの途中のあの台詞がめちゃくちゃ噛みそうになりました。
I almost stumbled over those spoken lines in the middle.
特にあのワンツースリーフォーファイブシックスセブンエイトのところがちょっと、
Especially the 'one-two-three-four-five-six-seven-eight' part...
滑舌が回らなさそうな感じでちょっと焦ったんですけど、
It felt like my tongue wouldn't keep up, so I panicked a bit...
ちょっと皆さんどうだったでしょうか？
How was it for all of you?
ということで今回は誕生日ということでですね、
Anyway, since today is my birthday...
ステージがちょっと一新しまして可愛くなりました！
...the stage has been revamped and looks so cute!
見て見て！めちゃ可愛いでしょ？
Look, look! It's so cute, right?
ちょっとこちら側見てください。
Take a look over on this side.
こちら側はね、でっかいクマちゃんがいるんですよ。
On this side, there's a huge teddy bear.
可愛いでしょ？
Cute, isn't it?
ちょっとねプレゼントもたくさんありまして
There are also lots of presents,
誕生日仕様にしていただきました！
all set up for my birthday!
なんと、なんと！反対側にこっちはですね、見てください！
And what's more! On the other side... look here!
見て！ぽよよも！
Look! Even Poyoyo!
可愛いソファ！なんかケツにリボンも付いてる...みたいな感じでですね、
A cute sofa! It even has a ribbon on its butt... and with all that,
すごい可愛くしていただきました。
they've made it all so incredibly cute.
誕生日なんでね、もうめちゃめちゃ可愛いをたくさん詰めていただきました。
Since it's my birthday, they packed in so much cuteness.
そしてですよ、みんなちょっと気づいたかな？
And also, did everyone notice?
ちょっとこのモニターの上を見て欲しいんですけど、
I want you to look at the top of this monitor,
見て！余のツノが付いてるんです！
look! It has my horns on it!
可愛い！上にもね可愛いバルーンたちがたくさん付いてるんですけど、
Cute! There are lots of cute balloons up there too,
ね、めっちゃ可愛いでしょ？今回作っていただきました！
right, it's so cute! They made it for this occasion!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そして今回のライブはですね、
And for today's live stream,
ハッシュタグ #百鬼あやめ生誕祭2023 となっておりますので、
we have the hashtag #NakiriAyameBirthday2023,
ぜひ皆さんハッシュタグつけてステージやらダンスやら、
so please use the hashtag to post about the stage, the dancing,
余のことやら、たくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいなと思います。
about me, and whatever else! I'd be so happy.
この後はですね、ゲストがたくさん登場しますので、
After this, lots of guests will be appearing,
一緒に歌って踊っていくので、ぜひ皆さんスクショやら撮ってくださいね！
we'll be singing and dancing together, so please take screenshots!
ということで、
And so,
この後も見てね〜！
keep watching!
Next
Are you ready?
ありえない幻想
Unbelievable fantasy
あふれだす妄想
Overflowing delusions
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
息をするように嘘ついても
Even if I lie as naturally as breathing
あたしやっぱいらない子？
Am I a useless child after all?
こぼれだしちゃった承認欲求
Overflowing desire for approval
もっとココロ満たしてよ
Fill my heart even more
アスパルテーム 甘い夢
Aspartame sweet dreams
あたしだけに愛をください
Give love only to me
救済執行
Salvation execution
ねー好きって言ってよ？
Hey, say you love me?
ありえない幻想
Unbelievable fantasy
あふれだす妄想
Overflowing delusions
止まんない つまんない 欲が散らばって
Unstoppable, boring desires scattered
求めてる愛情
The love I seek
隠してる劣情
The hidden base passions
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
Yeah
誰のこと見てんの？
Who are you looking at?
こういうの好きなの？
Do you like this kind of thing?
DDとかガチでやめてください
Seriously, please stop with the DD
かわいくなりたい！
I want to be cute!
キラキラしてたい！
I want to be sparkling!
もっともっとガチで褒めてください
Seriously, please praise me more and more
泣いちゃう燦々
I'll end up crying
開けちゃうシャンパン
Pop the champagne
今夜も配信来てくれるよね？
You'll come to the stream tonight too, right?
独占させてよ
Let me monopolize you
本命なんでしょ？
I'm your favorite, right?
もっともっとガチで推してください
Seriously, please support me more and more
飲み過ぎ注意オーバードーズ
Careful not to drink too much, overdose
クラクラさせていつだって
Make me dizzy, always
救済執行
Salvation execution
ねー好きって言わせて？
Hey, let me say I love you?
噛みついた衝動
The impulse that bit
戻れない焦燥
The impatience from which there's no return
止まんないミッドナイト 指が絡まって
Unstoppable midnight, fingers intertwined
ときめいた表情
A fluttering expression
何も言わないで
Don't say anything
君だけがボクの王子様
You alone are my prince
ありえない幻想
Unbelievable fantasy
あふれだす妄想
Overflowing delusions
止まんない 欲が散らばって
Unstoppable desires scattered
求めてる愛情
The love I seek
隠してる劣情
The hidden base passions
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
あたしだけずっと追いかけて！
Keep chasing only me forever!
ねー もう待てないの
Hey, I can't wait anymore
君以外全部いらないわ
I don't need anything but you
スキスキ絶頂症
作詞・作曲：koyori
Sukisuki Zetchoujou
Lyrics/Composition: koyori
満点採ったら褒め顔
If I get a perfect score, praise me
私はそんな貴方も素敵に見えるわ
Even that side of you looks wonderful to me
奇怪に起きた夏の戯れ
A strange summer play that occurred
もしやのもしや貴方に近づく好機会
Perhaps, just perhaps, it's a great chance to get close to you
ねえ…
Hey...
どきりとしちゃうでしょ
It'll make your heart skip a beat, right?
もう純情ぶって偽っちゃって
Stop pretending to be innocent and faking it
好き好き絶頂症
Love love peak condition
溶けちゃう前にさす
Before I melt, I'll sting
貴方が頬張って
You stuff your cheeks
噂になって強がっちゃって
Becoming a rumor and acting tough
妄想絶好調
Delusions are in top gear
呼び捨てにしてよ
Call me by my name without honorifics
合点いかぬ蒸した夜
A humid night that makes no sense
眠れず明くる朝まで貴方をひたすら
Unable to sleep, I think of you until the next morning
すってんころり滑稽に
Tumble over comically
紳士に助けられたくて淑女を被る
Wanting to be saved by a gentleman, I play the lady
ねえ…
Hey...
あの娘を見ないで
Don't look at that girl
もう考えたって抗ったって
No matter how much I think or resist
好き好き絶頂症
Love love peak condition
ベタベタしちゃうから
Because things will get sticky
もっと欲張って
Be more greedy
恋愛成就にあやかったって
Even if I'm blessed with successful love
妄想どっちつけ
Which delusion should I pick?
すれ違う貴方
You, passing by
駄目駄目な私
Good-for-nothing me
ミルク味の溶けたアイス
Melted milk-flavored ice cream
熱くなり赤くなる掌と頬
Palms and cheeks becoming hot and red
垂れる垂れるぽたり落ちる
Dripping, dripping, plop it falls
指伝い腕伝い甘い味
Sweet taste trailing down fingers and arms
もう純情ぶって偽っちゃって
Stop pretending to be innocent and faking it
好き好き絶頂症
Love love peak condition
溶けちゃう前にさす
Before I melt, I'll sting
貴方が頬張って
You stuff your cheeks
噂を聞いたどうやら本当
Heard the rumor, apparently it's true
好き好き痛いんだ
Love love it hurts
鳴呼　ねえ…　鳴り止まぬ
Ah, hey... It won't stop ringing
Next
YOU
Are you ready
ヘイ！ちゅー！ヘイ！ちゅー！
Hey! Kiss! Hey! Kiss!
心からあい！ヘイ！ちゅっ！ちゅっ！ちゅっ！ちゅっ！
From my heart, love! Hey! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
ベイビーあいへいちゅー
作詞：ナユタン星人 / ナナヲアカリ
作曲：ナユタン星人
Baby I Hate You
Lyrics: Nayutan Seijin / Nanawo Akari
Composition: Nayutan Seijin
わえはっきり言うけどベイベー
Hey, I'll say it clearly, baby
あたし　なにからなにまであなたがノーセンキュー
I'm "no thank you" to everything about you
ヘイ！ちゅー！ヘイ！ちゅー！あい！ヘイ！ちゅっ！ちゅっ！
Hey! Kiss! Hey! Kiss! Love! Hey! Kiss! Kiss!
ああ距離が近いほどベイベー
Ah, the closer the distance, baby
見えてくるくる気になるところの大バーゲン
I start seeing more and more things that bother me, it's a bargain sale
ヘイ！ちゅー！ヘイ！ちゅー！あい！ヘイ！ちゅっ！ちゅっ！
Hey! Kiss! Hey! Kiss! Love! Hey! Kiss! Kiss!
ほのぼのしてるこのお部屋で平穏はバイバイ
Bye-bye to peace in this heartwarming room
おんなじ世界じゃやってけない！
I can't live in the same world as you!
言ってるアレコレ通じてる！？
Are you getting all the things I'm saying!?
なにからなにまでわかってよ！
Understand everything from A to Z!
あなたなんてもういーや
I'm done with you
…とはいかない毎晩考えてる　もうベイベーベイベー
...it doesn't work that way, I think of you every night, oh baby baby
ベイビー・アイヘイチューが
Baby, baby, I hate you...
とまらない！
It doesn't stop!
これからさぁ
From now on,
あなたと何回やんの
How many times will we play
会話のドッジボール
Conversational dodgeball?
ベイビーベイビー・アイニーチューな
Baby, baby, I need you,
レベルでアイヘイチュー
at a level of "I hate you."
ウラのウラのオモテのハート
A heart on the surface's backside,
わかってほしんだよ
I want you to understand!
Hey! Hey!
もっと見てくれなきゃ
If you don't look at me more...
アイヘイチュー！
I hate you!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
気にしてくれなきゃ
If you don't care about me...
アイヘイチュー！
I hate you!
今日こそあなたに伝えなきゃ
Today I must tell you.
やっぱたまに素直が1番だもん
After all, being honest once in a while is best.
今まで冷たくしてたわけじゃないよ？
It's not like I was being cold to you until now, right?
勘違いやめてね
Don't misunderstand.
STOP!! STOP!!
誤解解きたいの気づいて！
Notice that I want to clear things up!
じゃないと知らないところに行っちゃうよ？
Otherwise, I'll go somewhere you don't know.
あのね　あたし　実はあなたのことが…
Um, you know, actually I...
なんて言えたらそれはもう大成功！！
If I could say that, it would be a huge success!!
…とはいかない毎晩反省会
...But it's not that easy; every night's a reflection.
ベイビーベイビー・アイヘイチューが
Baby, baby, I hate you...
おわらない！
It doesn't end!
これでまたあなたと何回やった？
How many times did I do this with you again?
「バイバイ」のチキンレース
A "bye-bye" chicken race.
ヘイトミーヘイトミーなほど離れられない
The more you hate me, the more I can't leave.
キライのウラにくっつくハート
A heart sticking to the back of "I hate you."
わかってほしい
I want you to understand.
Oh!
ベイビーベイビー・アイヘイチューが
Baby, baby, I hate you...
とまらない！
It doesn't stop!
このままさぁあなたと何回だって
Just like this, as many times as it takes,
ヘイトとアイのシーソーゲーム
a seesaw game of hate and love.
ベイビーベイビー・アイラブユーくらい
At a level of "I love you," baby,
言わせろよ！アイヘイチュー！
let me say it! I hate you!
ウラのウラじゃ伝わらないの
It won't reach you from the very back.
わかっているから
Because I know that.
それでもヘイト向けちゃうアイに
Still, for the love that points hate,
気づいてほしいの
I want you to notice.
Hey! Hey!
もっと見てくれなきゃ
If you don't look at me more...
アイヘイチュー！
I hate you!
Hey! Hey!
気にしてくれなきゃ
If you don't care about me...
アイヘイチュー！
I hate you!
Hey! Hey!
もっと見てくれなきゃ
If you don't look at me more...
アイヘイチュー！
I hate you!
Hey! Hey!
気にしてくれなきゃ
If you don't care about me...
アイヘイチュー！
I hate you!
アイヘイチュー、アイヘイチュー
I hate you, I hate you.
明日からアイヘイチューッッ
From tomorrow, I hate you-u-u!
MC忘れてましたーーー！
I forgot the MC section---!
ということで皆さん、どうだったでしょうか？ゲスト1曲目は「妄想アスファルトアメ」でした！
So everyone, how was it? The first guest song was "Mousou Asphalt-Ame"!
やぁ、どうだった？どうでしたか？え、ちなみにあくあと初めて二人で歌ったんですよ、3Dライブで。
Wow, how was it? How was it for you? By the way, it's the first time Aqua and I sang together in a 3D live.
あくあ、ありがとう！いや、「妄想アスファルトアメ」ね、めっちゃいい。あくあの歌っている板が可愛くて、余も一緒に歌いたいなと思って今回一緒に歌わせていただきました。
Aqua, thank you! No, "Mousou Asphalt-Ame" is really good. The way Aqua sings is so cute, and I wanted to sing it too, so I asked to sing with her this time.
そしてソロの「スキスキ絶頂症」、ちょっと余なんか...余っぽくないかなと思ってちょっと不安だったんですけど、ど、どうですか？どうですか？
And for my solo "Suki Suki Zecchoushou," I was a bit... I was worried it might not be very "me," but h-how was it? How was it?
あ、可愛い？あ、ありがとう、ありがとう。
Ah, cute? Ah, thank you, thank you.
そしてそして、三人、「ベイビー・アイヘイチュー」でねねちとあくあで歌いました！やったーー！可愛かったでしょ？
And and, the three of us sang "Baby I Hate You" with Nene-chi and Aqua! Yay! It was cute, right?
そして、みんなお気づきになられました？あの、余のこの右手に持ってる、左手ですね、持ってるこのメガホン！
And did everyone notice? Um, this megaphone I'm holding in my right hand—my left hand, I mean!
めっちゃ可愛いでしょ？見て！今回のね、ライブのロゴが入っております！見えるかな？
Isn't it super cute? Look! It has the logo for this live on it! Can you see it?
そして、あ！これ！これ気づきました？ぽよよのチャームがついてるんです！やったーー！これ超可愛いでしょ？
And, ah! This! Did you notice this? It has a Poyoyo charm on it! Yay! This is super cute, right?
なんかあの、「ベイビー・アイヘイチュー」のMVの中にメガホンと旗が出てくるんですけど、それをね、今回余のステージ仕様に作っていただきました！
You see, a megaphone and a flag appear in the "Baby I Hate You" MV, so I had them made to my stage specifications this time!
ありがとうございます！中ね、旗はね、あの...「余等」確か「かわよ」って書いてある大きい旗だったんですけど、
Thank you! Inside, the flag was... it was a big flag that said "Yo-ra" and "Kawayo," I believe.
あれは余の手書きで書いております！見てくれたかな？もしね、見逃しちゃった人間様、アーカイブでぜひ見てください！
I wrote those by hand! Did you see them? If any humans missed it, please check the archive!
そしてですね、みんな気づいた？Tシャツもこれロゴ同じなんですよ、メガホンと。これ可愛いでしょ？
And then, did everyone notice? The logo on this T-shirt is the same as the one on the megaphone. Cute, right?
ほらロゴね、めっちゃ可愛く作っていただきました。ありがとうございます。Tシャツ、ちょっとお腹出てるんですけど、ちょっと見ないでください。
Look at the logo, it was made so cute. Thank you. My stomach is showing a bit in this T-shirt, so please don't look.
そして見て！ちょっとカメラさんちょっと...気づきました皆さん？余、いつもブライト衣装スカートなんですよ。これ気づいたみんな？
And look! Camera person, could you... did everyone notice? I usually wear a skirt for my Bright outfit. Did everyone notice this?
余、今日ね、パンツスタイルなんです！見て！可愛いですカ？どうですか？ちょっとね、いつもスカート系なんでちょっと新鮮かなと思うんですけど。
Today, I'm wearing pants! Look! Is it cute? How is it? Since I usually wear skirts, I thought this might be a fresh look.
まぁちょっとこの後の曲中でもちょっとパンツスタイルが出てくるんじゃないかなーって思いますよ。そしてそして、ゲストもたくさん来ますので、
Well, I think this pants style might show up in some of the songs after this too. And and, lots of guests are coming as well,
お見逃しなく！見てね！
so don't miss it! Watch, okay!
Next YOU Are you ready
僕が最高だから
Because I'm the best,
有名になる
there's no need
必要ないでしょ
to become famous, right?
今日も配信待ちきれないね
I can't wait for today's stream either, you know?
この手紙を渡せば想いが伝わるかも
If I give you this letter, maybe my feelings will reach you.
まあ渡さないんだけどね
Well, I'm not going to give it to you, though.
ちょっと待って知らない
Wait a minute, I don't know.
言わない
I won't say it.
何も怪しいこととかないけど言えない
There's nothing suspicious, but I can't say it.
聞かないで
Don't ask me.
君の心を教えてよ
Tell me what's in your heart.
君のモストフェイバリットな態度で
With your most favorite attitude,
僕の心は壊されてしまう
my heart will be broken.
大抵なんて言えるからでもないから
It's not like I can usually say it,
もうわかんない
so I don't know anymore.
君は完璧だから
Because you're perfect,
有名になりたい
I want to be famous.
だけど僕は猛反対
But I'm strongly opposed.
僕が最適になる運命で
I'm destined to be the best for you,
怒らせちゃダメだから完全防備で
so you can't get me mad, I'm fully guarded.
最低な思い出作ったって
Even if we made the worst memories,
塗り替えてくれるよ何回も
you'll overwrite them, many times.
僕が最高だから
Because I'm the best,
有名になる必要ないでしょ
there's no need to become famous, right?
今日の配信耐えきれない
I can't stand today's stream.
あの人はあの人と付き合ってるらしいよ
Apparently that person is dating that person.
配信者もいいよ
Streamers are good too.
もしかしたら私も
Maybe I am too...
ちょっと待って知らない
Wait a minute, I don't know.
誰様?
Who do you think you are?
何もやましいこととかないけど言えない
There's nothing shady, but I can't say it.
やめたくないし
I don't want to stop,
あなたの心教えてよねえ
so tell me what's in your heart, okay?
君の笑顔で僕の心は癒やされていくの
My heart is being healed by your smile.
最低なんて思えるはずもないよね
There's no way I could think it's the worst, right?
けどわかんない
But I don't know.
僕は最低だから
Because I'm the worst,
有名になりたい君を求める純愛者
I'm a pure lover who wants you to be famous.
君の最適になる運命で
I'm destined to be the best for you,
諦めちゃダメだから完全勝利で
so you can't give up, it's a complete victory.
最低な恋で終わったって
Even if it ended with the worst love,
メルカリで買えるよ何回も
you can buy it on Mercari, many times.
僕が安定だから
Because I'm stable,
有名になる必要ないでしょ
there's no need to become famous, right?
今日も配信待ちきれない
I can't wait for today's stream either.
恋人じゃないのに
Even though we're not lovers,
あれこれ言われる意味もないのに
even though there's no meaning in being told this and that,
この胸のときめきは何なの?
what is this thumping in my chest?
君は完璧だから
Because you're perfect,
有名になりたい
I want to be famous.
だけど僕は猛反対
But I'm strongly opposed.
僕が最適になる運命で
I'm destined to be the best for you,
怒らせちゃダメだから完全防備で
so you can't get me mad, I'm fully guarded.
最低な思い出作ったって
Even if we made the worst memories,
塗り替えてくれるよ何回も
you'll overwrite them, many times.
僕が最高だから
Because I'm the best,
有名になる必要ないでしょ
there's no need to become famous, right?
今日の配信耐えきれない
I can't stand today's stream.
Next YOU Are you ready
ねえ。
Hey.
チューして?
Will you kiss me?
チュープリ踊りたいな
I want to dance Chuupuri.
ネットで炎上しちゃうかな
I wonder if I'll go viral on the net?
有名になったとき
When I become famous,
彼氏がいたら
if I have a boyfriend,
ヤバイかな
would that be bad?
まれいに生きてなきゃ応援してもらえないのかな
I wonder if I won't get supported unless I live purely?
黒歴史上等な私じゃちょっと
I, for whom dark history is just fine, am a bit...
ヤバイかな
worried if it's bad?
十字架背負う覚悟無いのなら
If you're not prepared to carry the cross,
その有名私にくれよ
give that fame to me!
生き急いでるわかってんだよ
I'm living in a hurry, I know that.
だって今の私は今消えちゃう
Because the current me will disappear now.
もう
Already...
あーあーあー アイドル・キル・ユー
Ah, ah, ah, idol kill you.
あーあーあー アイドルになって
Ah, ah, ah, becoming an idol,
君のこと好きになりすぎたのは
the one who fell too much in love with you
私のほうなの
was me.
会いに来て
Come see me,
会いたい!
I want to see you!
あーあーあー アイドル・キル・ユー
Ah, ah, ah, idol kill you.
あーあーあー アイコン変えよう
Ah, ah, ah, let's change our icons.
どんな私がキャッチー?
What kind of me is catchy?
んで、もっとその先の微々たる乙女を見てね
And, look more at the tiny maiden beyond that, okay?
愛してる
I love you.
チュープリプリンセス
Chuupuri Princess.
チュッ
Mwah
気づいていたの
I noticed it,
私の名前のTシャツの下に
under the T-shirt with my name on it,
透けてるあの子の文字
the letters of that girl are showing through.
That girl's letters shining through
どっちが本命よ？！
Which one is your true love?!
一生背負う覚悟がなくたって
Even if you're not ready for a life-long commitment
お手軽好きになっていいよ
It's okay to just like me casually
私生活とか色々あって
Life gets complicated, but...
だって今は私で幸せでしょ
...right now, you're happy with me, right?
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, I don't kill you
年の差ある君でも
Even if there's an age gap between us
どこかは私に似てる
You're like me in some ways
んでなんか許せないとことかあったとしても
Even if there are things about you I can't stand
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, I don't kill you
全部好きだよ
I love everything about you
君が君であるディテールのひとつに
If I can be one of those details...
私が立っていられたらそれは
...that make you who you are...
なんという...
...then that would be...
チュープリリンセス
...a Chu-Pri Princess!
ねえ、私の可愛いとこ100回言って！
Hey, tell me 100 things you love about me!
う〜かわいーでちゅね。黙って！
Ooh, you're so cute. Shut up!
セクシー！
Sexy!
顔、髪、肌、あと何？
Face, hair, skin, what else?
オーバーパワー！
Overpowering!
いつでも一番可愛いよ〜
You're always the cutest~
あ〜でもぶっちゃけ知ってるからさ。
Ah, but honestly, I know...
自分で可愛いと思えないとこ
...the parts of myself I don't think are cute.
君に好きでいてほしいんだもん！
I just want you to love them too!
ねえ、もっとチューしてよ！
Hey, give me more kisses!
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, I don't kill you
あ ああ アイドルになって
Ah, ah, ever since I became an idol...
君のこと好きになりすぎたのは私の方なの
...I'm the one who ended up loving you too much.
会いに来て 会いたい
Come see me, I want to see you!
あ ああ あいどんきるゆー
Ah, ah, I don't kill you
あ ああ アイコン変えよー
Ah, ah, I'll change my icon
どんな私がキャッチーよ
To whichever version of me is most catchy to you
んでもっとその先の微々たる乙女を見てね
But please also see the delicate girl beyond that
愛してる
I love you
チュープリリンセス Chu!
Chu-Pri Princess, chu!
Are you ready
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Surprise
Service
We are スティーレ！！
We are Stile!!
さあ 扉を開けて 未知なるパラダイス 体験しよう
Now open the door and experience an unknown paradise
おいで おいで You
Come on, come on, you
そう キミを待つのは 不思議なオアシス
That's right, what awaits you is a mysterious oasis
ほっこり日常に ちょっぴりSpice
A little spice for your cozy daily life
くーるん くーるん かきまぜちゃうんだ
Round and round, we'll mix it all up
ぷーるん ぷーるん 当店自慢のフレイバー
Boing, boing, it's our shop's pride and joy flavor
サービス サービス ご褒美タイム
Service, service, it's reward time
おもてなし ココロ込めて
Hospitality, from the bottom of our hearts
Welcome to わーい！
Welcome to— Yay!
わたし達と一緒に めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
Together with us, in a dazzling wonder daydream
愛情マシマシ 煩悩ナデナデ
Love extra large, desires petted
誠心誠意つとめます
We'll serve you with all our heart
いぇーす！ キミの元気チャージに
Yes! To recharge your energy...
ひと役買えるかな
...maybe we can play a part
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも
This kind of feeling, that kind of feeling...
意外と悪くないでしょ？
...isn't so bad, right?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, buono, I want to blend...
キミにキュンキュンキュン ハートにパンチパンチパンチ
...my heart throbs for you, a punch to the heart
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, buono, I want to blend...
お口に合いますか？
Does it suit your taste?
お口に合うといいな♪
I hope it suits your taste♪
千客万来！
A full house!
ちょっと、なんか不本意ながらも
Wait, even if it's a bit reluctant...
いつだって需要は斜め上
...demand is always off the charts
そんじゃ、いっか ホントのわたしは
Well then, okay, the real me is...
シークレットモードで 営業スイッチオン
...in secret mode, business switch on!
くーるん くーるん かきまぜてもっと
Round and round, mix it even more
ぷーるん ぷーるん キミ仕様のフレイバー
Boing, boing, a flavor just for you
サービス サービス 極上タイム
Service, service, premium time
癒やしとは かくあるべき
This is what healing should be
Welcome to わーい！
Welcome to— Yay!
わたし達のお店に 本日もようこそ
Welcome to our shop again today
おかえり待ってた
Welcome back, we've been waiting
リピートうれしいな
So happy you're a repeat customer
店員一同歓迎
All staff welcome you!
いぇーす！ キミのお疲れさまに
Yes! For your hard work...
ピッタリのレシピで
...with the perfect recipe
こーゆうのどうかな
How about something like this?
あーゆうのアリかな
Maybe something like that?
よろこんでもらえるかな
I hope you'll be happy
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Small
Strange
Serious
Selfish
Secret
ぱっぱっ！
Pappa!
We are スティーレ！！
We are Steal!!
さあ 扉を開けて
Now, open the door
愉快なパラダイス
A pleasant paradise
怖がらずにおいで
Come on in, don't be afraid
おいで（おいで）
Come on (Come on)
さあ いつも通りの毎日に
Now, to your everyday life as usual
イロドリと
With colors and
アソビゴコロ
a playful spirit,
召し上がれ
bon appétit
ブレンド・S
Blend S
Welcome to...
わーい！ 私達と一緒に
Yay! Along with us
めくるめく ワンダーデイドリーム
a dazzling wonder daydream
愛情マシマシ
Extra serving of love
煩悩なでなで
Petting your worldly desires
誠心誠意 つとめます
We'll serve you with all our heart
Yes! キミの元気チャージに
Yes! To charge up your energy
一役買えるかな？
I wonder if I can play a part?
こーいった感じも
This kind of feeling
あーいった感じも
That kind of feeling
意外と悪くないでしょ？
Isn't it surprisingly not bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend
キミに きゅん きゅん きゅん
Throbbing for you
ハートに ぱんち ぱんち ぱんち
A punch to your heart
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend
お口に合いますか？
Is it to your liking?
お好み聞かせてね
Tell me your preferences
お口に合うといいな♪
I hope it's to your liking
白い雪のプリンセスは
The Snow White Princess is
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mirror, mirror, oh mirror
世界で一番可愛いガールなの？
Am I the cutest girl in the world?
やめてよ 棘のような視線迫る
Stop it, those thorn-like gazes are closing in
優しいフリした彼女が
She, who pretended to be kind
素敵な晩餐 もてなした
Served a wonderful dinner
そっと口に含めば
If I softly take a bite
笑み 薄れてゆく
My smile begins to fade
意志の中で 夢を見てる
I'm dreaming within my consciousness
いつかのおとぎ話 時が止まる
Like a fairy tale from long ago, time stops
お願い KISS で目を醒まして欲しいの
Please, I want you to wake me up with a KISS
白い棺から 連れ出すように
As if taking me out from the white coffin
突き刺さる憎しみは ドラマ的な事情
The piercing hatred is a dramatic circumstance
祈っても 王子様はまだ来ない
Even if I pray, the prince hasn't come yet
鏡よ鏡よ鏡さん
Mirror, mirror, oh mirror
ネクタイ任せや 頬に合図するから
I'll leave it to the tie or signal on my cheek
ねたみを買われてしまった
I ended up being envied
七人の小人はいるけど
The seven dwarfs are here, but
助ける素振りしらんぷり
They feign ignorance of helping me
そっと首を掴まれ
My neck is softly grabbed
笑み ひと粒の
A single drop of a smile
涙さえも 拭えなくて
I can't even wipe away my tears
呼吸もままならない 視界 伏せた
I can't even breathe properly, my vision darkened
消えそうだから 早く駆けて欲しいの
Because I'm about to disappear, I want you to run to me quickly
訳は聞かないで 応えられない
Don't ask why, I can't answer
望まない憎まれ 深い愛の二乗
Unwanted hatred, deep love squared
もうすぐで いなくなるのかな
I wonder if I'll be gone soon
途切れてく 命の音
The sound of life is breaking off
毒リンゴを食した 少女のように
Like the girl who ate the poisoned apple
眠りにつく
I fall into a slumber
お願い KISS で目を醒まして欲しいの
Please, I want you to wake me up with a KISS
胸の中の声 届きますか？
Can the voice inside my chest reach you?
階段を登ったら ドアを開けるだけで
If you climb the stairs, just open the door
見つかるよ
I'll find you
ああ...
Ah...
お願いKISSで 目を覚まして欲しいの
Please, wake me up with a kiss
白い棺から 連れ出すように
As if taking me out of a white coffin
突き刺さる憎しみは ドラマ的な事情
The piercing hatred is a dramatic circumstance
祈っても 王子様はまだ来ない
Even if I pray, the prince still hasn't come
消えてしまう
Before I disappear
その前に...
Before then...
なんでいつも そっけないのよ？
Why are you always so blunt?
クール気取っちゃって
Acting all cool
会いたいでしょ？ 恋しいでしょ？
You want to see me, right? You miss me, right?
素直になろうよ！
Let's be honest!
それなら君の気を引いちゃいます
Then I'll grab your attention
ドキドキ溢れる 大作戦♡
A heart-pounding grand plan♡
1分 2分 3分 4分...
1 min, 2 min, 3 min, 4 min...
ほら既読スルーするんだ LINEを未読スルー
See, you're leaving me on read, ignoring my LINEs
「最近なんか気になって仕方ないんだよなー」
"Lately, I can't help but find myself interested in you..."
そんな感じで毎晩ずっと
Like that, every night, for a long time
何度も何度もきっと
Over and over again, surely
SNSチェック しちゃうでしょ？
You check my SNS, don't you?
ほらもっと夢中に なって！(＞◡＜)
Come on, get more hooked! (＞◡＜)
わざとあげた このストーリー
I posted this Story on purpose
君の足跡 チェックするの
To check your footprints
あざといなんて 言わないで
Don't call me calculate-ly cute
だって Love you Love you Love you 好きだっちゃ！
Because Love you, Love you, Love you, I like you!
わざと遅い 既読通知
A purposefully slow 'read' notification
私の心 非公開
My heart is set to private
鍵をかけた 恋心
A locked-up heart in love
ねえほらほらほら 私を気にして もっともっと
Hey look, look, look, pay attention to me more and more
私の声で 君が笑うから
Because my voice makes you laugh
その瞬間を切り取って 即保存しちゃいたい
I want to capture that moment and save it instantly
そのために心 奪っちゃいます
I'll steal your heart for that reason
明日は君の 誕生日
Tomorrow is your birthday
5分 4分 3分 2分
5 min, 4 min, 3 min, 2 min
おめでとうって わざと早まって
Saying congrats earlier on purpose
「ごめん、誰より早く伝えたかったんだ」
"Sorry, I wanted to tell you before anyone else."
そんなこと言えば あっという間
If I say that, in the blink of an eye
チョコレートみたい 溶けちゃうね
It'll melt away just like chocolate
もう早く振り向いて(,,> <,,)
Come on, turn around already (,,> <,,)
わざとあざと エキスパート
An expert at being intentionally cute
私の心 のぞいてよ
Take a look into my heart
タイムラインは 君ばかり
My timeline is full of you
もっと Love you Love you Love you ドキドキキュン！
More Love you, Love you, Love you, Heart-pounding kyun!
君だけに 限定公開
A limited-release just for you
足跡つくの 待ってるのに
Even though I'm waiting for your footprints
このまま行けば ログアウト
If things stay like this, I'll log out
そのままでやだやだやだ 私を愛して ずっとずっと
That's no, no, no, love me forever and ever
やっと見れた
I finally saw it
君のアカウントを
Your account
やっぱり君も
Just as I thought, you
私を好きなんだね
Love me too, don't you?
わざと全部君のためなんだから
Because I did it all for you on purpose
落ちちゃえばいいんだ
You should just fall for me
だけど私 少し反省
But I'm reflecting a little
あまり試すの 良くないね
Testing you too much isn't good
やけに遅い 既読通知
An awfully slow 'read' notification
やっぱ気になる！ なる！
I'm worried after all! Really!
わざとあげた このストーリー
I posted this Story on purpose
君の足跡 チェックするの
To check your footprints
あざといなんて 言わないで
Don't call me calculate-ly cute
やっぱ Love you Love you Love you 好きだっちゃ！
Still, Love you, Love you, Love you, I like you!
わざと遅い 既読通知
A purposefully slow 'read' notification
私の心 非公開
My heart is set to private
鍵をかけた 恋心
A locked-up heart in love
ねえほらほらほら 私を気にして もっともっと
Hey look, look, look, pay attention to me more and more
まさか君も わざとなの？
Could it be that you're doing it on purpose too?
わざとあとでエキスパート！
Waza to Ato de Expert!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
あれ？あれ？あれ？みんななんか...
俺今日、みんなスカート履いて...
Wait? Wait? Wait? Everyone...
Today, I had everyone wear skirts...
スカート履いたよ！
I wore a skirt!
初めてスカート履いた！
It's my first time wearing a skirt!
あざといめら、あざといめら...
Calculatedly cute, calculatedly cute...
ちょっと待って、よっちゃんもよっちゃんも
あざと構えきました...
Wait a second, Yocchan and Yocchan
have their 'calculatedly cute' poses ready...
なんかあざといユニットじゃないですか、ちらって。
Don't we look like a 'calculatedly cute' unit?
そうなんです今日はね、あざとい曲だったので、
みんなにスカート履いていただきました。
That's right, since it was a 'calculatedly cute' song,
I had everyone wear skirts today.
イエーイ！
Yay!
可愛いですよ。
You're all so cute.
なんかこのメンバー既視感があるんですけど。
I feel a sense of déjà vu with this lineup.
確かに！
True!
去年もなんかね、去年ね、みんなに歌って...
Last year too, last year we all sang...
踊ってもらいましたね、歌って踊りました。
and danced together, didn't we? We sang and danced.
ちょっとあの、ドキドキしちゃって...
ドキドキしました。
I was a bit, you know, nervous...
I was really nervous.
今回もなんで呼んでくれたんですか？
Why did you invite us again this time?
え、去年ちょっと反響が良かった。
Well, the response was really good last year.
イエーイ！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm so happy!
ユニット化しちゃいます？
Should we make this an official unit?
え、いいんですか？いっそ。
Wait, is it okay? Let's just do it.
気に入ってくれたってことですもんね。
It means you liked working with us.
ま、そうだね。
Well, yeah.
2回、3回目あるかどうかは、
ちょっとまだみんな次第。
Whether there's a 2nd or 3rd time
depends on everyone else.
みんな次第！？我々はややる気ですよ。
Depends on everyone!? We're totally up for it.
でもやっぱりほら、視聴者。
But you know, it's about the viewers.
結果が全て？結果が全てなんですか？
Results are everything? Are results everything?
出さないと。
We have to show them.
クイクイクイ...
Qui qui qui...
でもほらユニットで名前とか決まってないと、
みんな応援しづらいよね。
But if the unit doesn't have a name,
it's hard for everyone to cheer for us.
でもさっきちょっとみんなで話して...
ユニット名いろいろ考えて。
Actually, we talked about it earlier...
Thinking of various unit names.
とりあえずまず頭文字で、ほんの提案なんですけど...
For now, using our initials, it's just a suggestion...
なんですか？
What is it?
あまからっぺ！
Amakarappe!
なんかちょっと...田舎っぽ！
That sounds a bit... like a country bumpkin!
あまからに、「ぺ」は田舎者の方じゃなくて、
ペチーノとかの「ぺ」、甘いやつです。
In 'Amakara', the 'pe' isn't for country folk,
it's like the 'pe' in Pecino, the sweet kind.
ペチーノ？
Pecino?
なんか田舎っぺみたいな声偉いよ、大丈夫？
Your voice sounds a lot like a country bumpkin, is it okay?
うちらが、集まった時はペチーノって呼ぼうじゃん。
When we get together, let's call ourselves Pecino.
ペチーノ流行らそう、ペチーノ！
Let's make Pecino a trend, Pecino!
いいじゃん、ペチーノ。他に有望なユニット名ありますか？
Pecino is good. Any other strong unit name candidates?
でもなんかみんなの英語でかっこよく、CRUMPみたいな。
But maybe something cool in English with our initials, like CRUMP.
CRUMP！
CRUMP!
でも今のところあまからっぺが一番頭には残る...
But for now, Amakarappe is the one that sticks in the head most...
あまからっぺになっちゃうんで...
It's gonna end up being Amakarappe...
はしゃいでるけどさ、結果が全てですよ。
We're having fun, but results are everything.
結果出せないならこのユニットは解散...
If we can't get results, this unit will disband...
まずいまずい！ちょっとみんな助けてください！
あまからっぺを助けてください！
That's bad! Everyone please help!
Please help Amakarappe!
切り抜いてみんな！
Clip this, everyone!
ゆが... ゆが... 潰れちゃう...
Warpi... warpi... I'm getting crushed...
あやめ先輩が、あやめ先輩が苦しそう！
重すぎた？どうしたんですか？
Ayame-senpai, Ayame-senpai looks like she's in pain!
Was it too heavy? What's wrong?
そんな疲れた体を癒すための、あれがあるんじゃ。
To heal such a tired body, there's that thing.
お？何があるんですか？
癒されたい時にはどこに行きたいの？
Oh? What is it?
When you want to be healed, where do you want to go?
グッズが！出るぞ！
Goods! Are coming out!
何だグッズ、グッズが出る！やったー！
What goods, goods are coming out! Yay!
疲れたあやめ先輩を癒す、そんなグッズは、ある？
To heal the tired Ayame-senpai, are there such goods?
そんなグッズは、こちらです！ドーン！
Those goods are right here! Bam!
百鬼あやめ 誕生記念 2023
Nakiri Ayame Birthday Celebration 2023
え、こちら温泉をテーマにした、
B2タペストリーがこちら出ま...す！やったー！
So, this is a B2 tapestry with a hot spring theme!
Yay!
こちらsaino先生に描いていただきました。
ありがとうございます。
This was illustrated by saino-sensei.
Thank you so much.
続きまして、ドーン！
ソープディスペンサーセット！
Moving on, bam!
Soap dispenser set!
こちら3本ご用意しております。3本！
We have three bottles prepared. Three!
シャンプー、コンディショナー、
ボディーソープで3本です！
Shampoo, conditioner, and body soap,
that's three!
こちら猫屋敷ぷしお先生に描いていただきました。
ありがとうございます。
This was illustrated by Nekoyashiki Pushio-sensei.
Thank you so much.
続きまして、ドーン！
お風呂おけも出ま...す！やったー！
Moving on, bam!
A bath bowl is also coming out! Yay!
こちらのイラストは、先生に描いていただいております。ありがとうございます！
This illustration was drawn by the illustrator. Thank you very much!
続きまして、ドン！
Next, boom!
こちら、お風呂マットも出ます！
A bath mat is also coming out!
お風呂上がりのね、この足拭きマットとしてぜひ使ってください！
Please use it as a foot mat after taking a bath!
続きまして、ドン！
Next, boom!
シチュエーションボイスが出ます！
A situation voice will be released!
こちら今回は、「まったり夜桜温泉デート」となっております！
This time, it's "Relaxing Night Cherry Blossom Onsen Date"!
温泉デート！
Onsen date!
ちょっと恥ずかしいんですけど、まあもしよかったら聞いてください。
It's a bit embarrassing, but please listen to it if you'd like.
ということでですね、誕生日記念フルセットは...
So, for the Birthday Celebration Full Set...
...箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードと、
...a foil-stamped replica signed postcard and,
数量限定は、直筆サイン入りポストカードとなっております。
the limited edition comes with a handwritten signed postcard.
え？
Eh?
ど、どうしました？
Wh-what happened?
あ、あれです。ボイスもさっきの...
Ah, that's right. The voice too, from earlier...
ボイスは、数量限定バージョンは「お風呂上がりの幸せな時間」ということで。
For the voice, the limited edition version includes "Happy Time After the Bath".
幸せな時間！フルセットの特典ボイスですね！
Happy Time! It's the bonus voice for the full set!
はい、特典ボイスついていきます！
Yes, the bonus voice is included!
あ、そう、さっき、数量限定バージョンは直筆サインカードがあって、
Ah, right, as I said, the limited edition version has a handwritten signed card,
なくなり次第、箔押し複製サインカードとなっております。
and once they're gone, it will be the foil-stamped replica signed card.
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you for your support!
はい、皆さん、今日は来てくれてありがとうございました！
Yes, everyone, thank you for coming today!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ぜひ、来年もよろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to next year as well!
バイバーイ！ありがとうございました！
Bye-bye! Thank you very much!
頑張ります！
We'll do our best!